[
  {
    "index": 0,
    "question": "Video Player , Blue Color icon with while design , allow to Zoom Video like pics",
    "answer": "MX PLAYER"
  },
  {
    "index": 1,
    "question": "chatting app , Green \u0026 white icon , Used by 5bilion people  ",
    "answer": "WHATSAPP"
  },
  {
    "index": 2,
    "question": "Social Media Platform , watch Video , That is You",
    "answer": "YOUTUBE"
  },
  {
    "index": 3,
    "question": "Red Yellow white purple icon , Weight is Gram , where you shoot With filter , Process is Instant",
    "answer": "INSTAGRAM"
  },
  {
    "index": 4,
    "question": "i am Blue \u0026 White , i am Book , You can Upload Your Face on me",
    "answer": "FACEBOOK"
  },
  {
    "index": 5,
    "question": "Weight in Gram , White icon , Tell me Name",
    "answer": "TELEGRAM"
  },
  {
    "index": 6,
    "question": "king of Board game , 4 player Board Game , Made in india Game , Gametion Technology Made This",
    "answer": "LUDO KING"
  },
  {
    "index": 7,
    "question": "Browser , 4 Colour Icon , Liked By Most People",
    "answer": "CHROME"
  },
  {
    "index": 8,
    "question": "Allow You To Click Pic , AI Blur Images",
    "answer": "CAMERA"
  },
  {
    "index": 9,
    "question": "Manage Preferences , INBUILT in every device, ",
    "answer": "SETTING"
  },
  {
    "index": 10,
    "question": "Virtual Storage 15gb free , Trusted Provider",
    "answer": "GOOGLE DRIVE"
  },
  {
    "index": 11,
    "question": "Academy Where You Study Virtually , Online Lecture , Online Video on YT , Educational App",
    "answer": "UNACADEMY"
  },
  {
    "index": 12,
    "question": "Study with 2 Teacher Advantage ðŸ˜‚ but Virtualy , Brand Embracing Shahrukh Khan",
    "answer": "BYJUS"
  },
  {
    "index": 13,
    "question": "Cart where Add Any thing like U flip Your Phone , Shopping app ",
    "answer": "FLIPKART"
  },
  {
    "index": 14,
    "question": "Online Battle Royal Game , Best Graphic , Mutliplayer , A Region special verified Version Of Popular Mobile Game PUBG Mobile",
    "answer": "BGMI"
  },
  {
    "index": 15,
    "question": "famous App for graphic designing on Android \u0026 The Lab Where You can design Graphics",
    "answer": "PixelLab "
  },
  {
    "index": 16,
    "question": "Application Loved By Girls , Yellow Icon , Camera With Filter",
    "answer": "Snapchat"
  },
  {
    "index": 17,
    "question": "Battle royale Game , 50 player , published by Garena in 2017",
    "answer": "FREEFIRE"
  },
  {
    "index": 18,
    "question": "Online Shopping App , Published by Jio , Red in Color",
    "answer": "JIO MART"
  },
  {
    "index": 19,
    "question": "Music Streaming App , Green \u0026 3 Black curve line in it",
    "answer": "SPOTIFY"
  },
  {
    "index": 20,
    "question": "Music Streaming App , By Jio , u can also set hellotune in jio",
    "answer": "JIO SAAVN"
  },
  {
    "index": 21,
    "question": "world\u0027s largest source of information , starts with wiki",
    "answer": "Wikipedia"
  },
  {
    "index": 22,
    "question": "Listen to Audiobooks , Stories \u0026 Podcasts , Starts with Pocket",
    "answer": "Pocket FM"
  },
  {
    "index": 23,
    "question": "App by Google , Make UPI Payment , Net Banking",
    "answer": "Google Pay"
  },
  {
    "index": 24,
    "question": "Browser to Access DarkWeb , Private browsing without Traking , Starts with T",
    "answer": "Tor Browser"
  },
  {
    "index": 25,
    "question": "Online Food Order , Food Delivery and Dining , Starts with Z",
    "answer": "ZOMATO"
  },
  {
    "index": 26,
    "question": "Used to Calculate , System App",
    "answer": "Calculator"
  },
  {
    "index": 27,
    "question": "Instagram in A very Low Size",
    "answer": "Instagram Lite"
  },
  {
    "index": 28,
    "question": "Facebook in A very Low Size",
    "answer": "Facebook Lite"
  },
  {
    "index": 29,
    "question": "Twitter in A very Low Size",
    "answer": "Twitter Lite"
  },
  {
    "index": 30,
    "question": "Order Food , groceries , Starts with S",
    "answer": "SWIGGY"
  },
  {
    "index": 31,
    "question": "New App , Summary , All News in 60 Words Only",
    "answer": "INSHORTS"
  },
  {
    "index": 32,
    "question": "Find Relevant Job , search job , remote work , get salary",
    "answer": "LINKEDIN"
  },
  {
    "index": 33,
    "question": "App that helps us to find the Direction , either East West North or South",
    "answer": "COMPASS"
  },
  {
    "index": 34,
    "question": "Live Cricket Score , Commentary and everything else related to Cricket , Buzz",
    "answer": "CRICBUZZ"
  },
  {
    "index": 35,
    "question": "famous game , Endless , Climb Hill , Physics Based driving game ",
    "answer": "Hill Climb Racing"
  },
  {
    "index": 36,
    "question": "identify unknown callers , that is true , block spam calls amd sms",
    "answer": "Truecaller"
  },
  {
    "index": 37,
    "question": "imo in a very low size",
    "answer": "imo lite"
  },
  {
    "index": 38,
    "question": "online shopping deals , pink and white , That is Snap",
    "answer": "SNAPDEAL"
  },
  {
    "index": 39,
    "question": "order eye glasses , sun glasses , Lens \u0026 Frame online",
    "answer": "LENSKART"
  },
  {
    "index": 40,
    "question": "Enjoy With Tom who Repeat Your Voice , You can Manage \u0026 Take care of that Tom , App/game name ?",
    "answer": "MY TALKING TOM"
  },
  {
    "index": 41,
    "question": "Enjoy With Tom who Repeat Your Voice , You can Manage \u0026 Take care of that Tom , Upgraded Version ",
    "answer": "MY TALKING TOM 2"
  }
]